You work for
the Knights?
You've got
some nerve, Ted.
You're in your thirties,
still a nobody.
And you expect us
to believe
that you work for
the Knights?
I've taken the Knights
all the way to
the Super Bowl.
Took them all the
way to the Super Bowl?
You're trying to tell
me that the Knights
making it all the way to the Super Bowl
is thanks to you?
That's right.
Oh please.
Everyone knows
you're just a
washed-up cripple.
You're not even fit to clean the toilets.
And you're saying that you're responsible
for taking the Knights
all the way
through the finals.
Oliver,
your son's
not only broke,
he's obviously delusional.
I know my son.
He's not a liar.
Oh, really?
He doesn't lie, okay.
Then tell us, genius,
what exactly did you
do for the Knights?
I'm the head coach.